PIMPHUN CHAIWANICHSIRI

TEL: +6686 622 5221

EMAIL: pimphun.cha@gmail.com

Address: 317/9 Lardprow 94
 Wangthonglang Bangkok 10310

LinkedIn : linkedin.com/in/pimphuncha

Personal Statement

Over 6 years experience in digital field as an online web designer and coder, product owner and analyst, media planner and currently a digital marketer with a strong background in digital media with ability to plan, analyze and develop media strategy and business. A responsible and hard-working person with integrity, emotional intelligence and an open communication style. Proven leadership ability, capable of handling concurrent tasks under time pressure with problem-solving skills. A self-motivated, persevered, committed and reliable person. Quick Learner with passion for excellence.

Professional Experience



Online Marketing Manager

SPVi Public Co., Ltd

DEC 2015 - PRESENT

Thailand

- Planning, analyzing and developing online marketing media and project lead for E-Commerce products and campaigns to generate both online and offline awareness, engagement and lead to company sales and conversion.
- Participate and coordinate with company's partners to synchronize company's business requirement to enhancing business competitive advantage.
- Coordinate and lead internal teams to brainstorm creative idea and strategies against business requirement both online media and offline media.
- Presenting during company's meeting/calls. Also, monitoring, analyzing and report the performance with recommendation and action plan.



Manager, Exchange Planning (Digital)

mInteraction Co.. Ltd

MAY 2015 - DEC 2015

Thailand

- Planned, analyzed and developed digital media campaigns with strategies to generate effective awareness, engagement and lead conversions to meet the clients' business requirement.
- Gathered and analyzed media research information to developed media strategies and made strategic decisions for campaigns based on key performance indicators and trends.
- Coordinated with internal teams (online and offline team) to update, analyze the scope of clients' business requirement. Brainstormed creative idea and strategies against their objectives.
- Worked across various media channel (Facebook, SEM, GDN, Line, Email, etc.) to synchronize
 online and offline media, which generate the effective performance to meet clients' business
 requirement.
- Presented plan and strategy of campaign during client/partner agency meetings/calls.
- Monitored, analyzed and presented the campaigns' result performance for media with recommendation. Also, quarterly updated digital media trends with tactics and strategies to realize and plan the customers' marketing goals.

List of clients:

Allianz Ayudhya, S26, Dyson Thailand, Oriental Princess, Channel



Internet Marketing and Product Analyst

MAR 2014 - APR 2014

aCommerce Asia Thailand

- Responsible for all aspects of email marketing campaigns to promote a product or service by determines target audience, segmentation, devises campaign, and launches the campaign to create and generate leads for the business.
- Worked across other online marketing channels (ie. Facebook. SEO, Google and retargeting tools). Also, Cooperated with other online partner channels (ie. Line, TrueYou) to generate effective performance to meet business goal.
- Captured the relevant data, analyzed and provided analytical answers and insights as a result.
- Researched and reviewed for new technology, tools and strategies to drive the development of digital marketing.
- Coordinated with clients and internal teams to update, analyse the scope of client's work.
 Brainstrom creative idea and strategies to improve the performance of a client's site and campaign against their objectives.
- Presented the report and optimize email marketing campaigns, landing Pages, UX/UI, Sale Conversion with consult and recommend tactics and strategies to realize and plan the customers' marketing goals.

List of clients:

- E-commerce Online Store: Petloft, Venbi, Sanoga, Lafema, PowerBuy
- Central Group Fashion Online Store: THE OUTLET24, NexttoNormal
- English Institution: Wall Street English



Product Executive

True Corporation

JAN 2014 - MAR 2014

Thailand

• Coordinated with Customer Service Team and Business Team to plan, analyze and develop higher website performance to serve the best user interface and user experience.



Web Designer Specialist

MAY 2010 - JAN 2014

True Corporation

Thailand

- Responsible for designing and implementing website, mobile site, mobile application and digital TV Front-End. Also, managing digital content and widget design.
- Analyse Analysed and utilised user behavioural, need and experience information to develop, optimise and reorganise website user interface with better performance.
- Coordinated with marketing and technical team to plan, execute and optimise the business campaign, technical issues and website implementation.
- Researched and reviewed for new design and techniques to drive the development of company website.
- Contributed innovative ideas for strong and creative marketing campaigns.
- Supported marketing team with creative key visual (ie. banner, leaflet) and idea in marketing event and PR.
- Working with juniors and seniors to manage, evaluate, problem solving and decision-making.

List of work responsibilities:

TRUE Corporation website, True iContent Website, TrueMovie Website, True Academy Fantasia, The Voice Thailand, The Voice Kids Thailand, True Thai Flood

Skills

- Planning, Analyzing and developing strategy for online media.
- Coordinated and negotiate with clients and team about projects/campaigns with interpersonal skills.
- Ability to prioritize and handle multiple requests concurrently with problem solving skills.
- Presenting and reporting with analysis on performance and recommendation.

Tools and Applications

- Email Marketing (Campaign monitor, Mail Chimp)
- Google (Adwords, Analytics, Youtube)
- Social Media (Facebook, Instagram, Line)
- Graphic/Code (Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver)
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Power Point)
- iWork (Pages, Table, Keynote)

Programming Skill

- HTML (4,5) / CSS (2,3)
- JavaScript, Jquery
- Basic of PHP, SQL

Languages

- Fluent both Thai and English
- Basic of Chinese (Studying)

Education



Master of Information Technology

University of Technology, Sydney (GPA: 3.00/4)

2009 Sydney, Australia

Bachelor of Business Administration

(Major : Information System)

Mahidol University International College (GPA: 3.08/4)

Thailand

2004 - 2008

Extra Curricular Activities

- Co-founder of TW Fit Food Fun (Facebook Page : 2014-Present)
- Co-founder of The Plante' House (Facebook Page, Youtube Channel: Present)
- Act as a creative designer, content copywriting and video Editor, optimizer (2014 Present)

Analytics Certification

PIMPHUN CHAIWANICHSIRI

is hereby awarded this certificate of achievement for the successful completion of the Google Analytics certification exam.

VALIO THROUGH September 25, 2016



GOOGLE.COM/PARTNERS



AdWords Certification

PIMPHUN CHAIWANICHSIRI

is hereby awarded this certificate of achievement for the successful completion of the Google AdWords certification exams.



April 29, 2017

